좋아, 새 날이 밝았어
레이첼한테 그랬던 거?
All right, it's a new day.
That stuff about Rachel?
말끔히 사라졌어, 미쳤던 거지
넌 괜찮아, 그 정도가 아니지
You don't feel that now. It was crazy.
You're fine. You're better than fine.
친구 토니 말마따나 '왔다!'라구
You are, as your friend Tony
would say, "Great!"
모든 게 다 정상이야
걘 네 친구 레이첼이라구
Everything's normal.
She's just your friend, Rachel.
네 친구 레이첼, 네 친구 레이첼
Your friend, Rachel.
Your friend. Rachel.
- 안녕, 조이
- 네 여자 친구 레이첼이네!
-Hi, sweetie.
-Hey, it's your girlfriend, Rachel!
프렌즈 시즌 8
'챈들러의 새로운 취미'
자기 혹시 마약 했어?
Are you..? Are you high?
목욕하니까 너무 좋아
I just had the most amazing bath.
- 그래? 난 목욕 싫어해
- 나랑 하면 좋아할 걸
-Really? I don't like baths.
-You like them with me.
내가 싫어하는 건 목욕이지
물에 젖은 발가벗은 여자가 아냐
Honey, it's not the bath I enjoy.
It's the wet, naked lady.
- 목욕을 하면 맘이 편안해
- 그래? 뭘 하기에?
-Baths are so relaxing.
-Really? What do you do?
땟국물에 가만히
앉아있는 것뿐이잖아
You just sit in there,
stewing in your own filth.
내가 얼마나 지저분하다고 생각해?
How dirty do you think I am?
양초를 켜놓고 음악을 들으며
거품 목욕을 한번 해봐
If you had some candles and bubbles
and music, you would love it.
스트레스가 다 날아간다구
It would take all of your stress away.
지금은 수요일 2시고
난 로드 룰을 보고 있어
It's 2:00 on a Wednesday
and I'm watching Road Rules.
스트레스가 얼마나 있다 생각해?
How stressed do you think I am?
챈들러, 시간 좀 있어?
나랑 잠깐 얘기 좀 해
Hey, Chandler. You got a minute?
I really need to talk to you.
좋아, 식은 피자 먹을래?
아니면 먹다 남은 미트 로프?
Oh, yeah. Is this a cold-pizza talk
or a leftover-meat loaf talk?
됐어
Well, neither.
맙소사, 무슨 일인데?
Oh, my God, what's up?
그게 말야, 좀...
I don't know. It's just..
요즘 들어 내가...
Lately, I've been feeling..
까놓고 말 할께
Okay, here's what it is.
기분이 훨씬 좋아졌어, 고마워
You know what?
I feel a lot better. Thanks.
그러지 말고 이리 와, 몽 프레어
No. Come back here and talk to me,
mon frere.
- 누구?
- 그냥 와
-Who?
-Just come back.
알았어
Okay.
너랑 모니카는
오랫동안 친구였잖아
You and Monica,
friends for a long time.
둘 사이엔 규칙이 있었어
그런데 둘이 런던에 갔잖아
And sure, there are rules.
But then you went to London.
그런데 그건 달라, 거기도
규칙이 있거든, 내 말 뜻 알아?
But that's different. There are rules
there too, you know what I mean?
넌 아냐?
Do you?
두 사람의 경우는 달라
둘이 한 곳에 있었잖아, 안 그래?
It was different for you guys.
You were both in the same place, right?
- 런던 말야?
- 그래
-In London?
-Yeah.
그래, 함께 런던에 갔으니까
둘 다 런던에 있었지
Yes, when Monica and I were
in London, we were both in London.
있지, 공연한 말을 꺼냈어
이 얘긴 없던 걸로 해
You know what. This is a bad idea.
Forget all about it.
부탁이야, 오늘 대화는
우리 사이의 비밀로 해줘
And listen, do me a favor,
this conversation between you and me.
이게 대화라면
If that.
'센트럴 퍼크'
왜 자꾸 너만 빙고가 나오지?
How do I keep losing at tic-tac-toe?
안 돼, 내 동그라미는
늘 중심에 놔둬, 그게 규칙이야
Oh, no, no, honey.
My circle always stays in the middle.
로스, 내일 병원 가는 거 잊지 마
Oh, Ross, don't forget we have
that doctor's appointment tomorrow.
- 성별 검사할 거야?
- 아니, 우린 그런 거 안해
-To find out the sex of the baby?
-No. We don't wanna know.
그저 행복하고
건강하게만 자라주면 돼
All we care about
is that it's happy and healthy.
맞아, 행복하고 건강하고 귀엽게
Yep, happy and healthy. And cute.
- 똑똑하게, 과학도 좋아하고
- 인기도 많고
-And smart. With an aptitude for science.
-Popular.
지금 똑같은 애 얘기하는 거야?
Are you two talking
about the same baby?
- 이름은 생각해봤어?
- 그럼, 아주 많아
-Hey, have you thought of names?
-Oh, yeah. I've come up with a bunch.
- 정말? 나도인데
- 나도
-Really? Me too.
-Me too.
그래?
Really?
딸이면 피비고 아들이면 피보야
If it's a girl, Phoebe.
And if it's a boy, Pheebo.
글쎄, 하지만 만일의 경우를
대비하는 것도 나쁘진 않겠지
Maybe. But it wouldn't hurt
to have a backup, you know?
- 레이첼, 네가 생각한 건 뭔데?
- 뭐냐면 말야
-Rach, what were you thinking?
-Okay.
만약 딸이면
I was thinking if it's a girl..
산드린 어때? 불어식 이름이야
how about Sandrene? It's French.
세척제치고 이름이 아주 예쁘네
That's a really pretty name
for an industrial solvent.
- 알았어, 네가 생각한 건 뭔데?
- 남자 애 이름이야
-Okay, fine. What do you have?
-It's for a boy.
좀 흔하긴 하지만
I know it's a little out there, but..
다윈
Darwin.
맙소사, 학교 운동장에서
엄청 두들겨 맞겠군
Oh, my God. Our child will be beaten
to death in the schoolyard.
맞아, 산드린한테
Yeah, by Sandrene.
내가 산드린을 반대해서
너도 반대하는 거야
You're saying that
because I said no to your name.
그렇지 않아
I'm really, really not.
5회 거부권으로 하는 게 어때?
How about you each get five vetoes?
- 그게 좋겠다
- 거부권은 필요 없을걸, 들어봐
-That sounds fair.
-I don't think you'll need it. Check this out.
만약 딸이면 비
If it's a girl, Rain.
- 거부해
- 왜?
-Veto.
-Why?
비라구? "안녕, 내 이름은 비야"
Rain? "Hi, my name is Rain.
"난 전용 가마도 있고
내 옷은 밀짚으로 만든 거야"
I have my own kiln,
and my dress is made out of wheat."
나 걔 알아!
I know her!
데드 콘서트에서 나한테
집에서 만든 비누를 팔았어!
I bought a homemade soap
from her at a Dead show!
- 좋아, 아들이면 대처 어때?
- 왜 우리 애를 미워해?
-Okay. How about for a guy, Thatcher?
-Why do you hate our child?
- 알았어, 네 차례야
- 좋아, 제임스
-Fine, you go.
-Okay. James.
- 딸일 경우엔 말야
- 거부해
-But only if it's a girl.
-Veto.
난 루스가 좋더라, 루스가 어때?
I like Ruth. What about Ruth?
미안한데 애 나이가 89살이야?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Are we having an 89-year-old?
- 데이튼 어때?
- 거부해, 스튜어트
-How about Dayton?
-Veto. Stewart.
거부해, 소여
Veto. Sawyer.
- 거부, 헬렌
- 거부
-Veto. Helen.
-Veto.
내 귀가 이상한가?
거부란 말이 왜 정답게 들리지?
Is it me, or is Veto starting
to sound really good?
자기가 깜짝 놀랄 일을 준비했어
Boy, do I have a surprise for you.
발코니에서 섹스하게?
Sex on the balcony?
아니, 누군지 몰라도 참 끈질기네
No. But someone's not gonna
get over that idea.
- 뭔데?
- 목욕물 받아놨어
-What is it?
-I drew you a bath.
난 목욕 싫어한다니까
그냥 발코니에서 섹스하면 안돼?
I don't like baths. Could you draw me
a picture of us having sex on the balcony?
날 봐서 딱 한 번만 해봐
좋은 것만 썼단 말야
Please. Will you just try it for me.
I used all my best stuff.
양초도 켜놨지, 음악도 준비했지
목욕 소금이 든 거품 목욕이라구
I lit candles, I put on music.
I used bath salts, plus bubble bath.
게다가 해군 함선도 있어!
그야말로 남자식 목욕이라구
And got you this little plastic
Navy ship! So it's a boy bath.
- 이걸 보니 좀 당기네
- 일단 해보면 좋아할 거야
-This does butch it up a bit.
-I swear, if you try it, you will love it.
내가 목욕하면
발코니 섹스 좀 고려해 줄래?
If I do this, can we at least discuss
sex on the balcony?
물론이지
Absolutely.
고려한다고 돈 드는 거 아니니까
But I know how
that discussion's gonna go.
좋아, 나쁘지 않군 그래
꽃 향기가 아주 좋아
All right, this isn't so bad.
I like the flowery smell.
좋아해도 돼, 이 함선이 있잖아
Which is okay,
because I've got my boat.
긴장이 다 풀리는 듯한 느낌이야
I can actually feel my tension
just melting away.
잠들 것 같아
I could fall asleep in here.
익사할 것 같아
I could drown in here.
익사하겠어
Drowning.
- 어때?
- 맙소사
-So?
-Oh, my God.
좋아할 거라고 했잖아
목욕 끝나면 얼굴 마사지 해줄게
I told you you were a bath person.
Hey, maybe I can give you a facial.
더 큰 함선이 필요해
I'm gonna need a bigger boat.
맘을 열고
루스란 이름을 떠올려봐
I don't think you had an open mind
about the name Ruth.
꼬맹이 루스 겔러, 귀엽지 않아?
I mean, come on, little Ruthie Geller?
How cute is that?
맙소사, 마작 놀이하는
소리가 다 들리네
Oh, my God, I can practically
hear the mahjong tiles.
검사 결과 이상은 없어요
혹시 태아 성별을 알고 싶어요?
Okay. All your tests look fine. Are you
interested in knowing the sex of the baby?
- 아뇨
- 거기 적혀있나 보죠?
-No, we're not.
-But you have it right there in that file?
딸인지 아들인지?
You could tell us
whether it's a boy or a girl?
데이튼인지 산드린인지?
피비인지 피보인지?
Dayton or Sandrene?
Phoebe or Pheebo?
네, 하지만 궁금하지 않다면...
That's right.
But if you don't wanna know..
- 궁금하지 않아요, 그렇지?
- 그럼, 그럼
-No, we wanna wait. Right?
-Right. Right.
금방 올게요
Oh, I'll be right back.
제가 상관할 일은 아니지만
I know it's really not my place..
피보란 이름은 좀 그렇네요
but please don't name
your child Pheebo.
어떤 애가 제일 못생긴 것 같아?
So which of these babies
do you think is the ugliest?
뭐? 레이첼, 그럼 안돼
What? Rach, come on, that's terrible.
다 아기잖아, 모두 다 예쁘다구
They're babies.
They're all beautiful.
- 왼쪽에서 3번째?
- 그래, 왜 날 째려보지?
-Third one from the left?
-Yeah. Why is it staring at me?
내 말을 듣고 있는 것 같아
혹시... 차트를 봤구나!
I think it knows I'm talking about it.
Don't you..? You're looking!
- 아냐!
- 내가 봤어!
-I didn't!
-I saw you!
그래, 봤어
하지만 성별은 못 봤다구
Fine, I did,
but I didn't see anything.
부끄러운 줄 알아!
못생긴 애가 널 심판할 거야!
Shame on you! Ugly baby judges you!
- 알았어, 하지만 난...
- 말하지 마! 알고 싶지 않아!
-Okay. But listen to me, I didn't..
-Don't tell me! I don't wanna know!
말하고 싶어도 못해
성별을 모른단 말야!
I couldn't even if I wanted to,
because I don't know!
정말 못 봤어, 알고 싶지도 않구!
잠시 어떻게 됐던 것 뿐이야
I swear I didn't see anything! I don't want
to know. It was just a momentary lapse.
어떻게 된 거 좋아하네
자제심도 없어?
Momentary lapse?
Don't you have any self-control?
그런 설교는 두 달 전에 했어야지
Okay. A couple months late
on the lecture, Ross.
챈들러?
Hello?
욕실에 있어, 잠깐 와줄래?
뭔가 잘못된 것 같아
I'm in the bathroom. Can you come in here?
I think there's something wrong.
그냥 여기서 기다릴께
You know what?
I think I'll wait out here.
욕조 안에 있어
I'm in the bathtub.
- 왜 그래?
- 목욕물을 잘못 받았나 봐
-What's wrong?
-I drew my own bath, but I did it wrong.
물은 미지근하고 소금은 안 녹고
이젠 완전히 짱박았네
The water's tepid, the salt didn't dissolve
and is now lodged places.
게다가 향도 잘못 섞었나 봐
유칼리 나무랑 카모밀라?
And the scents I used don't compliment
each other. Eucalyptus and chamomile?
- 왜?
- 목욕 소금 말야
-What?
-Bath salts.
거품이 일기 시작했어
They're starting to effervesce.
완전히 달라
It's different.
흥미롭군
It's interesting.
좋아, 대화 주제를 바꿔
Okay. Let's talk about something else.
그래, 좋아, 오늘 하루 어땠어?
Yeah. Sure. So, what was
going on with you today?
오늘 조이랑 이상한 얘길 나눴어
I actually had the weirdest
conversation with Joey.
규칙이 어떠네, 잘못됐네 아니네
He was talking about rules
and right and wrong.
- 나한테도 똑같은 얘길 했었어
- 자기한테도? 뭐랬는데?
-I had the same conversation.
-You did? What was he talking about?
나도 몰라, 맥베스에 출연했을
때만큼이나 횡설수설이더라구
He hasn't had this much trouble getting
out words since we saw him in Macbeth.
그날 밤 아주 힘들었지
That was a long night.
좋아, 같이 분석을 해봐
조이가 정확히 뭐랬어?
All right, let's break this down.
What exactly did he say to you?
규칙에 대한 얘기랑
사람들이 달라 보인댔어
He was talking about rules
and looking at people differently.
- 나한텐 그 말 안 했어
- 그럼?
-He didn't say that to me.
-What'd he tell you?
자기랑 나, 런던에 대한
얘길 하더라구
He was asking questions
about you, me and London.
그리고 이 셋을 엮어주는
규칙에 대해서도 말야
And the glue that holds
this all together, the rules.
좋아, 자기랑 나, 그리고 런던
Okay. So you, me and London.
사람들이 달라 보인다
Looking at people differently.
어쩌면 우리가 런던에서 한 걸
하려는 건지도 몰라
Maybe he wants to do what you and I
did in London with someone.
그럼 그 '규칙'은 뭐야?
But what'd he mean by "rules"?
잠깐만, 얘기를 하다
피비가 들어오니까 멈췄어
Wait. He stopped talking
the minute Phoebe came in.
- 피비가 달라 보이니까
- 피비는 친구잖아
-Because he was looking at her differently.
-And Phoebe is his friend.
그래서 규칙을 깼다고 생각한 거야
So he thinks that would be
breaking the rules.
맙소사, 조이가 피비랑
런던에서 그걸 하려는 거야!
My God, he wants to do it
with Phoebe in London!
- 안에 있어?
- 잠깐만!
-You guys?
-Just a minute!
- 트리비아니 부인이야
- 피비한테 아무 말하지 마
-That's Mrs. Tribbiani.
-You don't say anything.
내가 왜 해?
Why would I say anything?
우리 친구들이
세기의 사랑을 시작한다구?
That two of our friends could start
the greatest love affair of their lives?
얼마나 고마운지 몰라
다같이 애를 순풍 낳는 거야!
They would have me to thank.
Then we could all start having babies!
- 아무래도 위험해
- 자긴 여기 있어
-I'm not gonna let you say anything.
-You just stay here.
하느님!
Oh, God!
모니카, 다리미 돌려주러 왔어
Hey, Monica, I brought back your iron.
네가 썼어? 잃어버린 줄 알고
1달 전에 새로 샀어
Oh, you had that? I thought I lost it.
I got a new one a month ago.
잘됐네, 고장냈거든
Oh, just as well. I broke this one.
- 왜?
- 아냐
-What?
-Nothing.
난 말하면 안 돼
입도 벙긋해선 안돼
I really shouldn't say.
I'm really not supposed to.
알았어
Fine.
기분 좋은 얘긴데
It's a humdinger.
아쉽네, 얘길 못해준다니 말야
Well, then it's really too bad
that you can't tell me.
누가 널 좋아한대!
Somebody likes you!
챈들러야?
Is it Chandler?
- 아니!
- 그럼 그만 쳐다보라고 해
-No!
-Then tell him to stop staring.
조이야
It's Joey.
정말? 조이라구? 설마
Really? Joey? You don't say.
- 너도 관심 있어?
- 몰라, 몰라, 몰라
-Is it something you'd be interested in?
-I don't know, I don't know.
한편으론 '세상에, 덥썩 물까?'
You know, I mean, on the one hand,
"Mother, may I?"
그런데 또 한편으론...
But, you know, on the other hand..
안돼, 난 못해, 우린 친구라구
No. No, I can't. We're friends.
안돼, 난 우정을 지키고 싶어
Oh, no. I don't wanna risk
what we have.
네 말이 맞는 것 같다
조이한텐 네가 얘기할래?
I guess that makes sense.
You think you're gonna talk to him?
그럼, 조이가 상처 받는 건 싫어
Sure. I mean, it's Joey.
I don't want him to get hurt.
나 완전히 인기 짱이네!
챈들러에 이젠 조이까지
Well, I must say, I am on fire!
First Chandler, now Joey.
- 챈들러는 아냐, 조이만이야
- 그렇겠지
-Not Chandler. Just Joey.
-Sure.
생각을 좀 해봤는데
루스란 이름이 좋아졌어
You know what? I've been thinking about it.
I'm coming around on the name Ruth.
정말 루스라고 이름 지을까 봐
I think I would actually consider
naming our child that.
레이첼, 그게 어떤 의미인지
상상도 못할 거야
Rach, I can't tell you
how much that means to me.
잠깐만
Wait a minute.
루스란 이름을 싫어했잖아
그런데 왜 맘을 바꿨지?
Wait a minute. You hated the name Ruth.
Why would you change your mind?
그건 그 이름을 쓸 일이
없을 거라는 걸 알기 때문이야
Unless you know we're never
gonna have to use it.
차트를 봤구나, 아들인 거야!
You did see. You know it's a boy!
난 아무것도 못 봤어
그냥 맘이 변한 것 뿐이야
I didn't see anything.
I actually changed my mind about the name.
웃기지 마, 양보하는 척하다가
I don't think so.
You're giving me Ruth..
나중에 아들이 태어나면
so you get to name him
when it's a boy.
히스나 블레인, 세코이아로
이름 지으려고 하는 수작이라구
That's when you'll swoop in and
name him Heath or Blaine or Sequoia.
난... 세코이아라!
I would.. Sequoia!
- 거부해
- 알았어
-Veto.
-Fine.
아니면...
Unless..
아기가 딸이라는 걸 알아내고는
you anticipated
that I would figure all this out..
정말로 루스라고 이름 짓고 싶어
and you know that
it actually is a girl.
이 모든 계획을 꾸민 건지도 몰라
And you really do want her
to be named Ruth.
난 그렇게 어리석지 않아!
알았어? 루스는 제외시켜!
Well, I'm not falling for that!
Okay? Ruth is off the table!
- 루스라 부르고 싶댔잖아
- 이렇게는 아냐!
-But, Ross, you want the name Ruth.
-Not like this!
웬일이야?
What's up?
- 조이, 나 알아
- 뭘?
-Joey, I know.
-What?
- 나 안다구
- 뭘?
-I know.
-What?
- 네 맘 다 안다구
- 맙소사, 눈치챘어?
-I know about your feelings.
-Oh, my God, you do?
그래, 하지만 모니카와 챈들러는
특별 케이스야, 잘되긴 힘들다구
I'm sorry. Things worked out for
Chandler and Monica, but that's rare.
알아, 게다가 이건 두 사람의
경우보다 훨씬 더 복잡하다구
I know. And this is so much more
complicated than it was for those guys.
레이첼이잖아, 젠장
I mean, it's Rachel, for God's sakes.
젠장, 레이첼이잖아!
For God's sakes, it's Rachel!
알아! 걘 내 친구잖아
게다가 임신한 친구라구
I know! She's not only my friend,
she's my pregnant friend.
로스의 임신한 전처란 말야!
She's my pregnant friend
who's Ross 'ex!
그래, 그게 레이첼이지
Yeah, that's Rachel.
확실하게 일깨워주네
Beat me over the head with it.
어쩌지? 감정을 지우려고
끊임없이 노력해봤어
What am I gonna do? I keep trying
to get rid of these feelings.
어젯밤엔 잠도 안 자고
레이첼의 단점을 적어봤다구
I stayed up all last night and made a list
of everything I don't like about her.
- 들어볼래?
- 그래
-You wanna hear it?
-Yeah.
'저지방 마요네즈를 고집함'
이게 다야! 이게 다라구!
"She made me switch to light mayo."
That's it! That's all I got!
그런데 알아? 맛은 똑같은데
허리 살은 빠지더라
You know what? Tastes the same
and my pants fit better.
조이, 걱정할 거 없어
잠시 지나가는 열병일 뿐이니까
Joey, I think you're getting upset for
nothing. This is probably just a crush.
그럴까?
You think?
당연하지, 이런 건
금방 왔다 금방 사라진다구
Absolutely. You get this rush
of feelings, but then it goes away.
맞아, 금방 사라질 거야
잠시 앓는 열병일 뿐이니까!
Yeah, just a crush.
That's all this is. It's a crush!
난 조이야, 깊은 관계엔 안 빠져
I'm Joey. I don't get deep feelings.
물론이지, 열병은 누구나 앓잖아
There you go.
Crushes happen all the time.
나도 너희들한테 그랬는걸
로스랑 챈들러는 빼고 말야
I know I've had them for all you guys.
Except for Ross and Chandler.
- 너도 우리한테 그랬을 거야
- 뭐 별로
-And I'm sure you've had them for us.
-Not really.
아예 대갈못을 박아라
Throw me a bone here.
의사한테 전화해봤어
So I called the doctor.
- 이제 둘 다 성별을 알게 됐군
- 뭐라구?
-Now we both know the sex of the baby.
-What?
맞았어, 학생이 마침내
스승으로 성장한 거야
That's right.
The student has become the master.
- 로스, 정말이야, 난 몰라
- 됐어, 딸이란 거 알잖아
-Ross, I swear. I don't know.
-Oh, come on, you know it's a girl.
뭐라구?
A what?
정말 몰랐어?
You really didn't know?
- 딸이라구?
- 아니
-We're having a girl?
-No.
- 방금 그랬잖아
- 아냐
-That's what you said.
-No.
- 딸이랬어
- 그래, 미안해, 정말 미안해
-You said girl.
-Yes. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
아냐! 딸이라니!
I'm not! We're having a girl!
네가 애 아빠인 건 좀 그렇지만
어쨌든 딸이라니!
Sometimes I can't believe it's with you,
but still, we're having a girl!
그러게 말야! 나 말야
애 이름을 루스로 짓기로 했어
I know! You know what?
I'm putting Ruth back on the table.
그래, 우리 베이비 루스라 불러
Yes, we'll have ourselves
a little baby Ruth.
- 거부하게 해줘
- 그럼, 그럼
-Permission to veto.
-Yes, please.
이거 에센스 오일이야?
Do I smell essential oils?
응, 목욕하려고
잡지 가지러 가던 참이야
Yeah. I'm gonna take a bath.
I was just gonna get a magazine.
이게 무슨 짓이야?
What do you think you're doing?
아마 나쁜 짓이지?
Leaving my troubles behind?
신참이라는 건 아는데
이건 올바른 목욕 에티켓이 아냐
I know that you're new at this,
but this is unacceptable bath decorum.
에티켓은 탕에서 나간 후 챙길게
It's so hard to care
when you're this relaxed.
좋아, 목욕하고 싶으면 해
대신 함선은 압수야
Okay, fine. You can have the bath,
but I am taking your boat.
여자처럼 목욕한대요
Now you're just a girl in a tub.
안녕, 남자처럼 생겼네
Hi, bubbles. Manly.
조이랑 어떻게 됐나
보고하러 왔어
I thought I would drop by
and let you know how it went.
말했어?
You told her?
말을 하게 만들잖아!
화술이 보통이 아니더라구!
She pulled it out of me!
She's like a conversational wizard!
- 어떻게 됐어?
- 내가 아니었어
-How did it go?
-You were wrong. He doesn't like me.
리 메이저스가
널 좋아한단 얘길 듣고
How would you like it if I sent you
to Lee Majors' house..
그 배우 집으로 갔는데
and I told you he liked you
and you went there..
가보니 네가 아니더라면
기분이 어떻겠어?
and you found out that he didn't like you.
How would you feel?
- 난 상관 안 해
- 정말? 그 사람 섹시해
-I don't think I'd care.
-Really? Lee Majors is hot.
- 안녕?
- 욕실에 있어!
-Hello?
-We're in the bathroom!
- 왜?
- 즐겁고 편안한 시간이거든!
-Why?
-Because it's a relaxing and enjoyable time!
- 여기서 뭐 하는 거야?
- 맙소사
-What are you guys doing in here?
-Oh, my God.
달라 보이는 친구가
피비가 아니라면
A friend he's looking at differently,
but it's wrong.
- 그건 레이첼이야!
- 레이첼을 좋아한다구?
-It's Rachel!
-You like Rachel?
수선 떨지 마, 피비랑 얘기했는데
열병이야, 곧 사라질 거라구
It's no big deal. Phoebe and I talked.
It's a crush. It'll go away.
거품 좀 가운데로 옮겨
Dude, you gotta rearrange
your bubbles.
축하해
Mazel tov.
로스랑 너희들을 찾고 있었어
Ross and I were looking for you.
여기서 뭐 하는 거야?
이런 맙소사
What are we all doing in here?
Oh, my.
- 여보, 배로 가려
- 항공 모함이 아니잖아
-Honey, cover it up with the boat.
-It's not an aircraft carrier.
안녕?
Hello?
여기 있어, 어서 빨리 들어와!
We're all in here,
and we'd love for you to join us!
이봐! 다들 뭐 하는 거야?
멋진 보트네, 이런
Well, hey! What's going on?
Oh, cool boat. Oh, no.
- 말했어?
- 아니, 널 기다리고 있었어
-Did you tell them?
-No. I was waiting for you.
- 말하다니 뭘?
- 딸이래
-Tell us what?
-We're having a girl.
정말?
Oh, wow! Really?
나중에 포옹해 줄께
I'll get you later.
좋아, 새 날이 밝았어
이건 열병일 뿐이야
All right. It's a new day.
And it's just a crush.
그렇고말고, 열병일 뿐이라구
That's all. Just a little crush.
내가 걱정하던 거?
그건 다 미친 짓이었어
All that worrying I was doing?
That was crazy.
내 친구 말마따나 '뻐꾹!'이라구
Like my friend the bird here
would say, "It was cuckoo!"
다 잘될 거야, 열병일 뿐이거든
Everything's gonna be fine.
It's just a crush.
- 안녕, 조이
- 사랑해
-Hi, sweetie.
-I love you.
같이 하니까 좋지?
It's nice to do this together,
isn't it?
그래, 지금 그거 너무 짜릿해
Yeah. And what you're doing
feels so good.
내가 아냐
I'm not touching you.
- 아니라구?
- 소금이야
-You're not?
-It's the salts.
희열의 새로운 장이군
Oh, sweet Lord,
new realms of pleasure.
발코니 생각만 안 해준다면야
Whatever keeps you
off the balcony, big guy.